Bradbury, M. mss. III 1950-2000 LMC 2695
Lilly Library
- Modern American Novel – Nabakov/Pynchon/black humour (Box 127)
- American novel in the 1960s and 1970s (Box 127)
- Politics of the liberal imagination – lecture version (Box 127)
- Liberal imagination article – background (Box 127)
- Modernism (Penguin) – introduction (Box 127)
- Forum lecture – A Changing Language (Box 127)
- Lectures on modernism (Box 127)
- Lecture – The Avant Garde and modernism (Box 127)
- Lecture – Some Cities of modernism (Box 127)
- Arthur Miller – article and research (Box 128)
- After Dinner Game – correspondence and reviews (Box 128)
- Who Do You Think You Are? – letters, reviews, material (Box 128)
- Parodies (Box 128)
- Sterne articles and comic novel (Box 128)
- American realism and romance of Europe – article (Box 128)
- E.M. Forster, (4ff.) (Box 128)
- Articles on Jane Austen, (2ff.) (Box 128)
- How I invented America (Box 128)
- Fanny Hill, (2ff.) (Box 128)
- An Age of Parody – talk/Encounter version, (2ff.) (Box 128)
- Putting in the Person (Box 128)
- A Dog Engulfed by Sand, (2ff.) (Box 128)
- The State of the Novel (Box 128)
- The Novel and Realism (Box 128)
- European literature (Box 128)
- American Novel, 1800–1900 – useful notes (Box 128)
- American Novel (Box 128)
- Edgar Allan Poe (Box 128)
- Whitman (Box 128)
- Lecture material on American Naturalism and California naturalism (Box 128)
- Miscellaneous photographs (6 and one postcard) (Box 128)
- Chest x–ray (Box 128)
- American novel book, chap. 3 – Anderson & Lewis (Box 129)
- The American fifties – photocopies (Box 129)
- Lecture on Modern American poetry (Box 129)
- American poetry of the 1920s (Box 129)
- Forms of Change in American writing (Box 129)
- American novel book – bibliographical/lists of novels (Box 129)
- Expatriates thesis: bibliography and notes (Box 129)
- Library work (Box 129)
- Second countries – MLR article (Box 129)
- The language novelists use (Kenyon Review) Towards a poetics of fiction (novel) (Box 129)
- The writer's predicament – article (Box 129)
- John Fowles' The Magus – article (Box 129)
- The Future of American Studies (Box 129)
- Parody article for Hoffman (Box 129)
- An Age of Parody – talk for BBC Radio 3, (March 1977) (Box 129)
- The comic novel – lecture and course notes, (3ff.) (Box 129)
- Comedy – Drue Heinz (Box 129)
- Certificate of eligibility for exchange visitor status – form (Box 129)
- British Council lecture tours –, 1967–1998 (Box 129)